Dear viewers all over the world, the devil wants us to curse Jesus while under situations.
The devil wants us to curse Jesus while under pain, affliction, poverty.
Our situations are tests to mature us.
Don't allow any situation to control you.
Don't allow any situation to mislead or overwhelm you.
Stay and cope with hard and good moments.
Viewers, listen. Stay and cope with hard and good moments.
A person can be sick in body and yet be a Christian, a friend of God,
a favourite of Jesus.
Don't measure your Christian life by your situation.
Don't allow your situation to mislead you.
I want to pray with you.
Viewers all over the world, whatever situation you are in,
in the name of Jesus, I release you!
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever you are passing through, right now, be released, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever situation you are going through in your life, be released, in the name of Jesus!
You situation, I say, 'Go!' Leave my people, leave their business,
leave their career, in the name of Jesus!
I can see you being released.
Where there is no vision, people perish.
I can hear breakthrough in your way, health, career and destiny.
Breakthrough, in the name of Jesus!
Thank You, Jesus, for their breakthrough, in Jesus Christ's name!
Viewers all over the world, I will know before you that you are free.
I say to you that you are free, in the name of Jesus!
I can see you being set free.
Whatever situation in your health, any area of your organs that is not functioning,
be it your kidneys, liver, blood, fluid or bones, be restored, in the name of Jesus!
Be restored, in the name of Jesus!
You are restored!
I can see you being restored!
It's a vision - I can see you being restored, in the name of Jesus!
Thank You, Jesus!
Those of you who are under the influence of my voice -
you believe Jesus is Lord, Healer, Deliverer, Saviour.
I say to you, this is your testimony - testimony of your health!
This is your testimony - testimony of your finances!
This is your testimony - testimony of your breakthrough!
This is your testimony - testimony of your restoration!
I can hear breakthrough once again.
Breakthrough!
Thank you, Jesus!
I rejoice with you, in Jesus Christ's name!
Amen!
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances, sermons
and testimonies from The Synagogue Church of All Nations.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations, and Changing the world!